# James D. Kim

- Diamond Bar, CA CELL (909) 342-0400 E-MAIL bronze10000@gmail.com
- PORTFOLIO https://bronze10000.github.io/portfolio/

**PROFILE** 

As a full-stack web developer with a background in research and eCommerce, I bring my love of learning and an analytical mindset honed from conducting experiments on a lab bench. My ultimate goal is to write awesome code as I continually improve my craft as a web developer.

**EDUCATION** 

### **Web Development Immersive**

**General Assembly** 

1933 S. Broadway, Los Angeles, CA 90007

**B.S.** in Botany

University of California, Davis 1 Shields Ave, Davis, CA 95616

**SKILLS** 

HTML & CSS **Javascript** Ruby Liquid **Ruby on Rails Bootstrap** MongoDB **PostgresSQL** ZenCart Wordpress **JQuery** Git SEO Ecommerce Shopify **Ebay** SASS

**EXPERIENCE** 

#### Contract web developer at The Joy Factory

November, 2016-currently

- Heavily modify company Shopify website (Liquid, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS)
- Modify company microsite (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)
- Search Engine Optimization of company web presence

## Freelance web developer

since April, 2014

- Develop Wordpress websites
- Develop Zencart websites
- Develop Shopify websites

Tutor Spring, 2015

- Teach bioinformatics
- Explain current research in caloric restriction of yeast
- Use R Packages to conduct bioinformatics research using available datasets

Researcher Spring, 2012-2014

• Studied role of Ecdysone Receptor, isoform A, in Aedes aegypti mosquito

## **Research Specialist**

2005-2012(Spring)

• Studied G-protein signaling in filamentous fungus, Neurospora crassa

Research Associate 1994-2002

Plant Pathology department of Seminis Vegetable Seeds, Co.

REFERENCES Available upon request